坏夜晚
编剧：史蒂文·莫法特
喂
Hello?
他不在这儿 你是哪位
He's not there. Who's speaking?
不好意思 哪里的王子
Sorry, the Prince of where?
哪一个
Which one?
不 哪一个王子 不是哪一个威尔士
No, no. No, which prince? Not which Wales.
呃
Um...
这是哪一年
What year is this?
我想那是找我的
I think that's probably for me!
端好这个
Hold this.
喂
Hello?
是的 一切都很好 别担心
Ah, yes, everything's fine. Don't worry.
当然了 为什么要担心啊
Well, exactly. Why should you be worrying?
谁提到要担心了
Who even mentioned worrying?
她好的很 你妈妈很好
She's fine. No, your mum is fine.
不许接这个电话 只有我才能接这个电话
Don't answer this phone. I answer this phone.
你去哪儿了
Where have you been?
一个派对 派对而已
Party. just a party.
呃 是的 你妈妈的确在这儿
Um, yes, your mum is here, actually,
但她现在没办法接电话
but she can't come to the phone at the moment.
呃 她在忙呢
Well, she's busy.
你懂的 英联邦的事
Oh, you know, the Commonwealth.
是您的儿子 夫人 他想和您通话
It's your son, ma'am, he wants to talk to you.
不能让他看见你这个样子
We can't let him see you like this,
或者听见…虽然也没办法听见你
well, hear you, not that he could hear you,
你是条鱼啊
you're a fish.
抱歉我有另一个电话进来了
Sorry, I've got another call coming in.
喂
Hello?
大呼小叫是没有用的 大使
There is not a bit of use yelling, ambassador.
您的将军正困在我的塔迪斯里
Your warrior chief is trapped in my Tardis.
除非你把女王陛下变回人类的样子
And until you've turned Her Majesty here back into a human being,
他只能待在这儿 别担心 他十分安全
he's staying put. Don't worry, he's perfectly safe...
等会儿别挂电话
just popping you on hold.
你干了什么
What have you done?
我以为那是只苍蝇
I thought that it was a fly.
屠戮亿万生灵这种事 就到此为止吧
So much for the slaughter of 10 billion souls.
究竟发生了什么
What is going on?
我在参加一场派对
I was at a party.
发生了一点小意外
There was a slight incident.
什么 意思是你夜里溜出去参加派对
What, so you sneak out at night to parties?
等一下 你还穿得这么整齐
Hang on. You're dressed up.
你什么时候穿着那么整齐过
You never dress up.
River 也在对吧?
Was River at the party?
她怎么会在那儿
Oh, why would she be there?
千万别对我说谎 博士
Don't... just don't lie to me, Doctor.
你太不擅长说谎了
You're rubbish at it.
听我说 我才没有溜出去参加派对
Look, I do not sneak out at night to parties
和…和…River Song
with-with-with River Song.
嗯 她还好吗
Hmm, how is she?
她很好
Fine.
看吧 一拆就穿
See? Rubbish.
听着 我错了 但我现在有要事要处理
Look, sorry, but I am in the middle of a thing.
博士
Doctor!
Doctor.
我…我得和你谈谈
I... I need to talk to you.
我睡不着是有原因的
There is a reason that I couldn't sleep.
RORY
Rory!
你干嘛
What are you doing?
你一脸严肃的样子
You've got the serious face on.
每次你一脸严肃 我就喊 Rory
I always shout for Rory when you've got the serious face.
Rory 她又在闹情绪了
Rory, she's having an emotion!
怎么了 Amy
What? What's wrong, Amy?
你叫他来干什么
Why are you calling him?
轮到他值班了
It's his turn.
你俩…你俩还轮流值班
You two have... You two have turns?
不
No!
这条鱼不对
It's the wrong fish.
我拿错鱼了
I've taken the wrong fish.
River 我们拿错鱼了
River, we've got the wrong fish.
呃 抱歉两位 我犯了个错误
Look, sorry, you two. I've made a mistake.
我还有三小时来拯救英联邦
I've got three hours to save the Commonwealth.
三小时以后会发生什么
What happens in three hours?
宠物商店要开门了
The pet shops are open.